Uh, all right, then.
Let's begin the Ultra Awesome Sports
Day Celebration Party (as named by Iko).
We're doing this
at your place, Lemon-chan?
It's cheaper to drink at home.
Yikes. She's already drinking,
so no toast.
Why'd you make us change
into these clothes?
School rules would be a pain
if you were in uniform.
Let's just say you're visiting
an older friend today.
The teachers' exam
must be bugged if she passed it.
You've got a nice place, Lemon-chan.
Who's gonna give the toast?
Who else but yours truly?
Take it away, President.
Good job, everyone.
Especially you, Shinobu.
Thank you.
A toast to Lemon-chan,
who's paying for everything.
Huh?
Cheers!
I'm paying? But I'm broke and
waiting for payday.
This is punishment
for slacking on advisor work.
Thanks for treating us.
Fine, whatever.
Anyway...
I said to change into something comfy.
But you went all-out with those outfits.
Why are you all dressed to kill?
Ah, I get it.
Good for you, Yamabuki.
You can produce an heir for your family.
Wha? What are you trying to say?!
You girls must've panicked because
someone made a proxy confession to him.
Ah, youth.
I-It has nothing to do with him.
This is just how I normally dress.
I-I just grabbed
whatever was nearby, too.
I just wanted to wear some new clothes.
Look at you, making excuses.
At least come up with some better ones.
And what's your excuse, Rikka?
I picked this out hoping
Yamabuki-kun would call me cute.
You heard her, Yamabuki. What do you say?
He's asleep!
I guess he did run around a lot.
I can't believe he fell asleep
in a woman's apartment.
Too bad for you, Rikka.
Huh...
You let a good chance slip, Yamabuki-kun.
You'll never see me in this outfit again.
Okay, the odd one's out for the count.
Let's have ourselves a girls-only party.
Why don't we go buy some food first?
How about we each bring
something we'd like to share?
Sounds good to me.
What do we do about Bucky?
Just put him on the bed.
Your place is fancier
than I expected, Lemon-chan.
I don't know about growing bean
sprouts in the bathroom, though.
What's wrong with that?
Easy access to water.
I wanted to ask you something,
but you had to go and fall asleep.
Say, why did Shinobu
hug you during the event?
You two have always hit it off.
Are you dating or something?
Oh, Iko's back.
NENE SAW
Have you two kissed and stuff?
Hoo boy, I forgot my wallet!
I think I set a new world
record for being forgetful!
W-Welcome back, Nene.
Huh?
You were here, Iko?
I just came back to grab my wallet.
Are you taking a break?
Y-Yep.
What'd you buy?
That's a secret.
Come on, tell me.
Wait, did I just try to get in Iko's way?
Why? Because she was gonna kiss him?
But it's got nothing to do with me.
Hey...
How long have you been here?
Huh?!
U-Uh, I just got back!
I didn't see or hear anything!
I dropped my contacts,
and my ears are full of fluff!
So, have you ever kissed anyone?
And here I was trying so hard
to change the topic!
Where'd that come from?
Dunno. Just felt like asking.
I have, yeah.
Really? Who? And when?
It was fairly recently.
If that one counts.
You're so grown-up.
You have, huh? Wow.
By the way, Iko...
Do you like the errand boy here?
Why do you ask?
I mean, you were about
to kiss him earlier.
You saw that? Y-You big fat liar!
You said you didn't see anything!
I'm sorry I have 20/20 vision!
It's your fault for being so careless.
Whoa, Iko?!
I don't think it's like that, but I dunno.
I've always been a recluse,
so it's the first time I've felt this way.
Do you have feelings for Bucky?
Not really. I really hate all boys.
But... well,
he's better than the other
boys I know, at least.
Are you saying...
I'm back!
Nene-chan? Iko-chan?
Huh?
That's weird.
Their shoes are here.
Did they go out in slippers?
Guess I'm the first one back, then.
Why are we hiding?
I dunno!
Yamabuki-kun's still asleep, huh?
That's too bad. I even bought
something nice for you.
Thing is,
I owe you two apologies.
First, I'm sorry for hugging you.
I thought we were done for,
so you were basically my savior.
I hope you didn't mind.
I certainly didn't.
The other thing I must apologize for...
is lying to you.
We're partners in crime,
but there's something I didn't tell you.
Maybe I'll fess up now.
You see,
back during the confession event...
I'm back!
Huh? Nobody home?
That's weird.
Did they go out in slippers?
Why are you two hiding?
I dunno!
Why are you hiding, Shinobu?!
Guess I'm the first one back.
He's still asleep?
Really? I got you something nice, too.
Hey!
Aw, such a shame.
I've gone and changed.
I'm sulking 'cause you
didn't compliment me.
Oh, wait. You can't hear me.
Wow, you're still playing the guitar?
I'm actually writing a song right now.
But I think I've hit a wall.
Achoo!
What in the world are you doing?
Crap, I fell asleep.
Wh-What's with this weird mood?
What's the matter?
Surely you're not fighting.
We did fight.
You did?!
That's not why, though.
It's not?!
We agreed to each buy something we like,
but we all bought the same thing.
Okay, but how'd you all end up
buying whole-ass cakes?
Did you want to eat cake that badly?
Well, you worked really hard,
so I wanted to thank you.
I wanted to celebrate our success, yep.
You were tired, so I figured
something sweet might help.
I just bought it because I wanted some.
But four cakes is too many, huh?
He dug in quick!
Yours truly just happened to have
the mother of all sugar cravings.
Four cakes might not even
be enough to satisfy it.
Yamabuki-kun...
Don't force yourself.
Don't make me laugh—
This is what I'd call...
Rejoice!
I bought cake!
Thank you for the treat.
Oh, wow.
I was moved by your efforts.
How many calories was that?
Are you okay?
No problem at all. That was delicious.
Eat my cake next, then.
My heart seeks entertainment.
This is a celebration.
Simply eating and drinking
would be a waste.
He noped out.
Something that would bring
the members closer together...
How about we play a game of some sort?
Good idea. Let's do it.
I wanna play Cats'n'Dragons.
Do you have any games, Lemon-chan?
Well, I do have some stuff
for drinking games.
The loser has to eat this in one go.
The devil is among us!
Don't just decide the punishment first!
You're joining us, right?
I pass. I avoid carbs past 8 PM.
And beer doesn't count?
How did she become a teacher?
Which one are we playing?
This one for sure.
I don't wanna use my brain.
And someone's probably good at it.
Smart. Yours truly hasn't lost a game
of Concentration in my 17 years of life.
It's your first turn. Don't overthink it.
Go for it, Nene-chan.
Softly...
Heck yeah!
I'm done.
That was quick!
Me next.
I don't play analog games like this often.
Huh?
It's exciting, huh?
Wha?
Yikes, you're going there already?
I upped the difficulty.
Taking no prisoners, huh?
What's your move, Yamabuki-kun?
Hmm.
Am I allowed to touch as many blocks
as I want, as many times as I want?
What do you say, ref?
Lemon-chan's the ref?
Don't see why not.
I have the ref's permission. Here I go.
Don't poke around too much.
You'll make it collapse.
Oho?
You're an expert at this, Yamabuki.
Please. We Yamabukis
just play it occasionally.
Three blocks on each level.
Fifty-four blocks in total.
In this old-school balancing game,
each block appears to be the same...
but they're slightly different
in size and thickness!
So you go for the slightly thinner ones!
Who's next?
Go ahead.
Don't get all smug on me!
You're pissing me off!
He thinks he's got this in the bag.
Yamabuki-kun's a tough nut to crack, huh?
Yeah, he hasn't noticed I changed.
Time to get serious, I guess.
Crap. All that cake's making me drowsy.
Will you hurry up?
One of these four is Apollo.
That'll work.
How about over here?
You can do it.
I dunno about that one.
Long time no talk.
Back then, it was definitely her
on the other side of the door.
What was the deal with
the proxy confession earlier?
I felt like I had to express my feelings.
I ran away from my radio show,
and I guess I'm just sick of hiding it.
While you're at it,
why not show yourself?
Yeah, I wish.
What if I said
I was actually fine with that?
That's why I asked you
to come here, anyway.
No, I'm good.
What?
I've decided to find you myself.
If you showed yourself now,
I would be admitting defeat.
And that goes against
the Yamabuki family tenets.
Besides, I made a promise, remember?
I'll turn everyone in the club into pros.
I'll know who you are
by then, like it or not.
You're actually serious about that, huh?
I don't think that dream's
going to come true.
What are you after, anyway?
Did you come here just to find me
and make me a pro?
I'm here for a personal reason.
I don't want to talk about them.
That said...
After hearing all your voices in person,
I've found myself a new goal.
I want to get a voice-related job, too.
Except, I won't be a performer.
I'll be a producer.
I want to release songs.
I want to produce anime.
I want to have concerts
and create broadcast programming.
I want to work with you.
Like it or not,
I'll make that dream come true.
And you're coming with me.
You're so self-centered.
I'm coming with you, huh?
Close your eyes.
H-Hey, did you just walk out the room?
Could you be any more daring?
That voice was...
Errand boy?
How long are you gonna space out for?
My bad. I was thinking about something...
What on Earth?!
If you think you can move a block now,
I'd love to see you try!
How'd it end up like this?
We did our best.
You got on our nerves.
The power of friendship.
I can't believe you four teamed up
to take down yours truly.
But is this even allowed?!
I say why not? It's fun.
Yay.
Remember, Lemon-chan craves
instant gratification above all else.
I can't say her response
comes as a surprise,
but I will say this isn't how
a teacher is supposed to be!
Okay, now, go ahead.
It's your turn.
Though, one touch and...
it's all o-ver for you!
I don't know, it might crash on its own.
My strategy has been nullified.
In which case, I'll have to
measure them with my eyes.
Victory is ours!
That was a good change of pace.
Hey, look at the moon.
How pretty.
Rawr!
Okay, werewolf.
Rawrity-rawr!
Aren't you more of a cat?
It's so beautiful.
You'll wake people up.
Apollo, may I say one last thing?
I was always a fan of yours,
and I still am.
I'm really glad I got
to hear your voice again.
So I'll return the favor and tell you
the same thing I said back then, too.
Arisu...
I love you.
Thank you for calling my name.
I got to hear Apollo's voice
in person for the first time,
but I still couldn't identify
which of these four was her.
Are you tired?
Today was a bit much, even for you, huh?
I had no time to breathe all day.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't fatigued.
That said...
You all must be just as tired.
We provided commentary
for all the events,
TEAM RED - TEAM WHITE
kept the score, and moved things along.
The broadcast club has cleared
every mission we had for sports day.
We should be proud of it.
Quit acting all smug, errand boy.
Don't take charge.
But yeah...
We really did pull it off.
The proxy confessions went over well, too.
It wasn't easy,
but we had fun, huh?
You had fun?
Of course we did.
That was cool.
I'd like to do more of these.
If you all had fun,
then yeah, it was a huge success!
I'm glad I went for it.
Nene-chan, Iko-chan, Rikka-chan,
and Yamabuki-kun...
Thank you all!
I'm coming with you, huh?
Close your eyes.
I'LL CHERISH WHAT YOU JUST SAID FOREVER
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Sriram Gurunathan
Mariana Martinez
William Haggard
Quality Check:
Translation Check:
S Bilyeu
Michelle Tymon